Let's take a look at the five statements on this quiz.
دعونا نلقي نظرة على العبارات الخمسة الموجودة في هذا الاختبار.
Number one was, when you type you udacity.com into your browser,
العبارة الأولى كانت: عندما تكتب udacity.com في متصفحك،
your browser communicates with Udacity's server using HTTP.
يتصل المتصفح بخادم Udacity باستخدام HTTP.
Well, that's true.
حسناً، هذا صحيح.
There were a bunch of things involved in getting a web page to your browser.
كانت هناك مجموعة من العوامل المشاركة في إيصال صفحة ويب إلى المتصفح،
But one of them is that your browser communicates with a server using HTTP.
لكن أحدها هو أن متصفحك يتصل بخادم ما باستخدام HTTP.
The browser sends a request for the page and the server responds.
يُرسل المتصفح طلباً للحصول على الصفحة ويستجيب الخادم.
What's in that response is number two,
ومحتوى ذلك الرد هو العبارة الثانية:
a piece of html.
ألا وهي كود HTML.
So, number two is true.
لذا، فإن العبارة الثانية صحيحة.
Number three says that your browser has to copy
العبارة الثالثة مفادها أن متصفحك عليه إرسال نسخة
all of the files from the web server. That's not true.
من جميع الملفات الموجودة على خادم الويب. وهذا ليس صحيحاً.
The browser only fetches a copy of the particular files or
المتصفح يجلب فقط نسخة من ملفات أو موارد معينة
So, number four is true.
إذن، العبارة الرابعة صحيحة.
Your browser requests other files from our server and other web servers.
يطلب متصفحك ملفات أخرى من خادمنا وخوادم ويب أخرى.
Number five says that everything on Udacity's website has to come from Udacity's server.
العبارة الخامسة مفادها أن كل شيء على موقع Udacity يجب أن يردنا من خادم Udacity.
That's not true. Web pages can include or
وهذا ليس صحيحاً. صفحات الويب يمكن أن تتضمن أو تشير إلى ملفات
For instance, this video isn't hosted on
على سبيل المثال ، لم تتم استضافة هذا الفيديو
the same server that provided the html around it.
على نفس الخادم الذي قدم كود الـ HTML الذي حوله.